Resume

David Skødt Lauritsen Tønballevej 5 7130 Juelsminde

Age: 26

Phone: 51 51 18 97 Email: seqlog@gmail.com

LinkedIn profile: linkedIn.com/in/DavidLauritsen



Personal & professional profile

I am young man with an avid interest in computer science, primarily focused on the interaction between system and user. Through my Master's Degree in Medialogy, I have honed my knowledge of interaction methods, as well as creating prototypes and proving their efficiency through statistical analysis. Medialogy is best described as a mixed bag of courses that range from system- and shader programming to human perception and cognition. I have am keenly determined to work with projects that might shape the future of technology. I hope to work for a company such as Google and Microsoft within the next five years, as I perceive them to be amongst the companies that bring about the most interesting changes and ideas in technology. From my graduation in the summer of 2015 to early February, I was in America, hiking 2.600 kilometers on the Appalachian Trail, an experience I will never forget. I love travel and I will gladly consider international job offers.

Education

2013-2015 Master of Science in Medialogy with a Specialization in Interaction

 Thesis title: Aurally Aided Visual Search Performance Comparing Virtual Audio Systems (published through Audio Engineering Society, presented at the "137th AES Conference" in Los Angeles, USA)

2010-2013 Bachelor of Science – Medialogy, Aalborg University

- Study focus: Interaction design, UX, programming, esthetics, objective- and subjective trials, sound, human perception and statistics
- Individual focus: 3D sound w/ HRTF, presence (immersion), image processing, system design, C++/C#, user experience
- Thesis: Differences in human audio localization performance between a HRTF- and a non-HRTF audio system (published through the Association for Computing Machinery, presented at the "8th Audio Mostly Conference" in Pitå, Sweden)

2010 Mathematics B, intensive summer course at VUC in Århus, Denmark

2006-2009 STX, lingual focus at Horsens Gymnasium in Horsens, Denmark

Work experience

2016 Temp. teacher at Glud Skole, teaching maths, English and Danish

2014 Internship at VOLUME in Copenhagen, Denmark

- Internship replaced the 9. semester in my MSc at Aalborg University
- I got to work on Local Heroes, one of the projects they hope to bring to the U. S.
- Focus on interaction, user-friendliness and scaling on a web-based platform
- Assisting coworkers and boss with general computer issues

2013 - 2015 Matcher at AAU Matchmaking

- Volunteer work with focus on establishing contact and cooperation between students at Aalborg University and local companies
- Focus on communication and networking

2010 Various temp. jobs through "Vikarene" in Horsens, Denmark.

2010 Recruit in the Military of Denmark, 4 months at the barracks in Varde, Denmark

2009-2010 Assistant teacher at lower grades (0. - 4.) at Glud School & after school programme

- Assistant to the teachers in grades with young troublemakers
- Helped students with school work and projects

Software qualifications

Programming languages: C#/C++, Javascript, ActionScript 3.0

Software experience: Unity3D, Game Maker, Maya, 3DS Max, Sony Vegas, Photoshop, LaTeX.

Microsoft office: Experienced in all office products

Languages

Danish: Fluent (5/5)

English: Fluent (5/5)

German: Good (3/5)

Spanish: Fair (2/5)

Hobbies and interests

I have a huge interest in software- and hardware development and I perceive myself as quite the geek. These interests keeps me constantly updated on the newest trends in games and technology. Aside from that, my hobbies include video editing, cooking, martial arts and outdoor adventures. The latter should be obvious due to my most recent trip to the United States, where I undertook the majority of the Appalachian Trail.